Prince,
أمير،
this is bad.
هذا سيء.
Listen to me, prince.
استمع إلي أيها الأمير.
Something bad happened, prince.
حدث شيء سيء ، يا أمير.
Something bad happened.
شيء ما سيء حدث.
Prince,
أمير،
things have changed.
لقد تغيرت الأمور.
It's him.
إنه هو.
The Cheng Da Lei Tiger Tally of Toad Village
تشنغ دا لي تايجر تالي بقرية العلجوم
was taken away by him.
تم أخذه بعيدا من قبله.
In order to take Black Rock City,
من أجل الاستيلاء على مدينة بلاك روك ،
I did not hesitate to commit myself to this,
لم أتردد في الالتزام بذلك ،
But you told me that
لكنك أخبرتني بذلك
you lost the Tiger Tally.
لقد خسرت Tiger Tally.
Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،
are you the one Han Huju likes?
هل أنت الشخص الذي يحب هان هوجو؟
I can't believe you really ruined my plan.
لا أصدق أنك أفسدت خطتي حقًا.
It seems that only by stopping the Prince of Rong Clan,
يبدو أنه فقط من خلال إيقاف أمير رونغ كلان ،
can we buy time for reinforcements.
هل يمكننا شراء الوقت للتعزيزات.
Hot-blooded young man,
الشاب ذو الدم الحار ،
I know how you feel right now.
أنا أعلم كيف تشعر الآن.
I still hope you can choose carefully.
ما زلت آمل أن تتمكن من الاختيار بعناية.
What will happen
ماذا سيحدث
if I run away from Black Rock City?
إذا هربت من بلاك روك سيتي؟
That's all I can say.
هذا كل ما يمكنني قوله.
But no matter what you choose,
ولكن بغض النظر عما تختاره ،
I will bless
سأبارك
your boss,
مديرك،
Let me meet him.
دعني أقابله.
Master,
يتقن،
you haven't recovered from Fuhu Jingang Pill
أنت لم تتعافى من حبوب فوهو جينجانج
last time,
آخر مرة،
what if
ماذا إذا
Shut up!
اسكت!
Who dares to take a step forward?
من يجرؤ على اتخاذ خطوة إلى الأمام؟
Expel Toad Village.
طرد قرية العلجوم.
This guy took my Three Axe of Heaven Opening,
أخذ هذا الرجل افتتاح فأس السماء الثلاثة ،
and the bonus of the three axes is only three moves.
ومكافأة المحاور الثلاثة هي ثلاث حركات فقط.
As long as you survive these three moves,
طالما أنك تنجو من هذه الحركات الثلاث ،
you may still have the strength to fight.
قد لا يزال لديك القوة للقتال.
Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،
do you know?
هل تعرف؟
Because you're in the way.
لأنك في الطريق.
How many soldiers
كم عدد الجنود
are going to die in Rong Clan?
سوف يموتون في رونغ كلان؟
So?
لذا؟
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
One move
خطوة واحدة
Two moves.
حركتان.
A warrior who fights with Han Huju head-on,
محارب يقاتل مع هان هوجو وجهاً لوجه ،
can you only dodge?
يمكنك فقط المراوغة؟
Three moves.
ثلاث حركات.
I won't hide anymore.
لن أختبئ بعد الآن.
I can't believe it's so powerful.
لا أصدق أنه قوي جدًا.
Master.
يتقن.
With this strength,
بهذه القوة ،
it seems that you are not enough to please me.
يبدو أنك لا تكفي لإرضائي.
There's no need for you to survive.
ليست هناك حاجة لك للبقاء على قيد الحياة.
Master,
يتقن،